<s:Envelope xmlns:s="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/soap/envelope/"><s:Body><SearchNewsResponse xmlns="http://tempuri.org/"><SearchNewsResult z:Id="1" z:Size="28" xmlns:a="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/NewsDAL.Model" xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:z="http://schemas.microsoft.com/2003/10/Serialization/"><a:NewsView z:Id="2"><Comments z:Id="3" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="4" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-07-24T16:24:54</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">4</ID><Keywords z:Id="5" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="6" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Amer Ali.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="7" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Amer Ali.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="8" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="9" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="10" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">new.law.maritime.sector</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="11">Dubai, United Arab Emirates &lt;br /&gt;
H.E. Ahmed Butti, Executive Chairman of Ports, Customs, and Free Zone Corporation, Executive Chairman of Dubai Maritime City Authority, confirmed today that the issuance of the Law No. 11 of 2010 regulating marine transport in the Emirate of Dubai, and outlining the scope and jurisdiction of the Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), represent a major step forward in supporting Dubai&amp;rsquo;s maritime sector, and the creation of a platform for higher levels of excellence and quality in Dubai maritime industry in general. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
H.E. Ahmed Butti emphasized in his statement that the new decree comes as a realization of the wise vision of His Highness Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Vice President and Prime Minister of the UAE, Ruler of Dubai, in supporting the economic growth of Dubai, and addressing the growing needs of the maritime sector. This decree will help provide compliance with international environmental and maritime standards (locally, regionally, and internationally), and will help create a safe and secure operation for all marine craft activities in all of Dubai waterways, regional and local.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The tasks, responsibilities, and jurisdiction of DMCA will help it create a &amp;ldquo;safe and vibrant maritime environment in Dubai&amp;rdquo; and leading positive change in the emirate by the introduction and support of maritime rules and regulations. All this will create a best-practice maritime environment in Dubai that will eventually bring higher customer satisfaction, enhanced cooperation with all government and non government parties involved in the maritime industry, and generate a lot of investment opportunities with high yield in the maritime sector.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
H.E. Ahmed Butti said on this occasion DMCA, represented by all its staff and teams, express great gratitude and appreciation to His Highness Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid, for the trust he bestowed on the maritime authority, and all pledge to do their best in achieving the DMCA goals, and supporting and serving the excellence model of Dubai, and its people and visitors alike. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
H.E. Ahmed Butti clarified that the DMCA administration, led by Amer Ali, the Director General of DMCA, will embark on setting all the strategies and operational mechanisms for the new law, and they will do this in the highest levels of professionalism and in full compliance with the international maritime standards &amp;ndash; so that the end product will live up to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s reputation of excellence, and will help enhance its position as a leading global maritime destination.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Amer Ali, the Director General of DMCA said that the new law has vested 14 powers in the authority handling issues such as inspecting; licensing and registering marine transport vehicles to make sure that technology, pilots and crew operating on such vessels meet and comply with standards and regulations in place. The wide-ranging legislation seeks to provide comprehensive oversight concerning marine activities through providing a set of clearly defined rules and guidelines to be enforced by appropriate authorities. Amer Ali added that this law will help Dubai streamline maritime sector related revenues, and centralize and unify the administration and management of this very important sector of the economy. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Realizing the important role human resources play in sustaining the maritime sector, DMCA established the Emirates International Maritime Academy (EIMA)&amp;ndash; a strategic initiative that supports the regional and international maritime industry through the development of qualified maritime expertise that meets growing needs of the sector. EIMA&amp;rsquo;s focus is to develop and improve the skills of future generations by enabling them to work onboard ships as officers and/or engineers. The academy also aims at providing various maritime courses that increases the efficiency of workers in ports and dry docks. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
H.E. Ahmed Butti said that by following the international standards set by the International Maritime Organization (IMO), EIMA will further enhance the UAE&amp;rsquo;s image as the regional capital of maritime excellence. The academy is dedicated to cooperating with the world&amp;rsquo;s leading maritime universities and academic institutions to further strengthen the region&amp;rsquo;s offering within maritime education.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Jobs in the maritime sector in Dubai increased by 15% in 2008, to 48300; while the overall maritime sector contributed with more than 9.9 Billion AED to the Dubai GDP in 2007.</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="12">New Law will Bring Higher Levels of Quality  and Excellence to the Maritime Sector in Dubai</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="13" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Id="14">en</b:LangCode><b:LanguageCulture z:Id="15">en-US</b:LanguageCulture><b:Name z:Id="16">English</b:Name></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2010-06-09T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Id="17">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/H.E. Ahmed Butti.jpg</a:NewsThumbnail><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="18" z:Size="3" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="19"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="20">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Amer Ali.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>835</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="21">Amer Ali</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="22">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Amer Ali.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="23"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="24">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/9 June 2010,/Bus.24-7.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>836</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="25">Bus.24-7 - 9/6/2012</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="26">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/9 June 2010,/Bus.24-7.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="27"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="28">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/H.E. Ahmed Butti.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>837</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="29">H.E. Ahmed Butti</b:Title><b:Url z:Ref="17" i:nil="true"/></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="30">H.E. Ahmed Butti, Executive Chairman of Ports, Customs, and Free Zone Corporation, Executive Chairman of Dubai Maritime City Authority, confirmed today that the issuance of the Law No. 11 of 2010 regulating marine transport in the Emirate of Dubai, and outlining the scope and jurisdiction of the Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), represent a major step forward in supporting Dubai’s maritime sector, and the creation of a platform for higher levels of excellence and quality in Dubai maritime industry in general.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="31">New Law will Bring Higher Levels of Quality  and Excellence to the Maritime Sector in Dubai</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="32"><Comments z:Id="33" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="34" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-07-24T16:36:39</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">6</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="35" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Ali Al Daboos.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="36" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Ali Al Daboos.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="37" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="38" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="39" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.jet.ski.registration</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="40">&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following to the issuance of the Law No. 11 of 2010 by HH Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the Vice President and Prime Minister of UAE, Ruler of Dubai, regulating marine transport in the Emirate of Dubai, the Jet Ski registration, licensing, and all other related processes - which were previously the responsibility of the marine department in Dubai Roads and Transport Authority, will be handled by Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) effective August 8th, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through its offices in Dubai Maritime City in Bur Dubai, DMCA will facilitate all various Jet Ski-related transactions for the public, including registration, inspections, issuance of license, renewal of license, amendment of license and cancellation of license. To ensure a smooth transition and no inconvenience to Jet Ski users, DMCA has informed all relevant government departments and concerned parties about the new structure and the specific responsibilities now being handled by the Authority, and launched a public awareness campaign outlining the new location, required details, and working hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"With DMCA assuming maritime regulatory responsibilities in Dubai, beginning with the Jet Ski operations, we are now well on course of realising His Highness' vision of creating a safe, vibrant, and world-class maritime environment in Dubai," said, Ali Al Daboos the Executive Director of DMCA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For his part, Mr. Essa Abdul Rahman Al Dossari CEO of RTA's Public Transport Agency said:&lt;/strong&gt; "We are pleased to give DMCA the opportunity to share and benefit from RTA's expertise in the registration and licensing of Jet Skis. We believe that due to its expertise in the maritime industry, DMCA will certainly provide great benefits to the Jet Ski communities, and the maritime sector and national economy - as well as promote efficiency, safety, and transparency in the delivery of services to the public,"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The establishment of DMCA realises the vision of H.H. Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, to create a fully integrated maritime environment that supports the sustained development of Dubai's strategic plan and contributes to the development of the national economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This move also comes in accordance with the Dubai Maritime City Law No. (11) of 2007 that was passed into law by His Highness Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum. The law tasks DMCA to enhance Dubai's position in the maritime industry, and to oversee the development of specific maritime sectors such as maritime services, maritime management, vessel and yacht registration, vessel and yacht ownership and charter, maritime and educational research, vessel and yacht design and building, maritime shipment organisation, maritime exhibition, conferences, training and workshops; maritime tourism and maritime specialised arbitration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This initiative is not only a simple transfer of functions from one government entity to another; it really represents a commitment to raise the level of performance and quality to meet and exceed the expectations of our clients in the maritime sector, locally, regionally, and internationally.  This will also help provide compliance with international environmental and maritime standards and will help create a safe and secure operation for all marine craft activities in all of Dubai waterways, regional and local." added Al Daboos.&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="41">Dubai Maritime City Authority to Handle  Jet Ski Registration and Licensing in Dubai </a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="42" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2010-08-01T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Id="43">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Ali Al Daboos.jpg</a:NewsThumbnail><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="44" z:Size="3" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="45"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="46">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Ali Al Daboos.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>858</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="47">Ali Al Daboos</b:Title><b:Url z:Ref="43" i:nil="true"/></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="48"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="49">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Jet Ski/Khaleej Times.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>859</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="50">Khaleej Times - 1/8/2010</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="51">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Jet Ski/Khaleej Times.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="52"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="53">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Jet Ski/GulfNews.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>860</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="54">Gulf News - 1/8/2010</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="55">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/Jet Ski/GulfNews.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="56">Following to the issuance of the Law No. 11 of 2010 by HH Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the Vice President and Prime Minister of UAE, Ruler of Dubai, regulating marine transport in the Emirate of Dubai, the Jet Ski registration, licensing, and all other related processes - which were previously the responsibility of the marine department in Dubai Roads and Transport Authority, will be handled by Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) effective August 8th, 2010.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="57">Dubai Maritime City Authority to Handle  Jet Ski Registration and Licensing in Dubai </a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="58"><Comments z:Id="59" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="60" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-07-24T17:11:15</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">14</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="61" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/MSS pict2 (2).jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="62" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/MSS pict2 (2).jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="63" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="64" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="65" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">final.stage.martime.sector.strategy</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="66">Dubai &lt;br /&gt;
United Arab Emirates&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Government and non-government entities working in the maritime sector of Dubai and associated with it, are reaching the final stages of the development of a comprehensive, first-of-its-kind maritime sector strategy (MSS) for the Emirate. The MSS will help Dubai lay the foundation for the creation of a sustainable and competitive maritime offering that will position Dubai at par with world leading maritime centers. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In a meeting that was held recently at the headquarters of Dubai Maritime City Authority by representatives from the strategy development teams involved in the project, it was announced that 80% of the strategy has been completed. The main goals and strategic aims of the new strategy are developed in line with the overall Dubai Strategic Plan, and are designed to support that strategy, in making Dubai a center of excellence in all aspects of the maritime industry. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The meeting was attended by senior officials from the strategy teams in the organizations involved in the development of MSS, and these include: Amer Ali, the Executive Director of DMCA, Ali Al-Daboos, Executive Director of Operations at DMCA, Bassam Abu AlSaoud, Director of Strategy and Corporate Support at DP World, Hamad Bin Mejrin, Executive Director, Government of Dubai Department of Tourism &amp;amp; Commerce Marketing, Sarah Ishaq, Chief Engineer, Transportation Planning and Policies at RTA, Faeq Maslama, Senior Maritime Specialist, Marine Transportation Department &amp;ndash; RTA, and other senior government officials. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The total number of government and non-government entities involved in the development of the Dubai MSS is 30.&amp;nbsp; These are divided into three main groups: an internal core team, an external core team, and an external consultative and support team.&amp;nbsp;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="67">Final Stage of Dubai Maritime Sector  Strategy Begins</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="68" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-05-16T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="69" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="70">Government and non-government entities working in the maritime sector of Dubai and associated with it, are reaching the final stages of the development of a comprehensive, first-of-its-kind maritime sector strategy (MSS) for the Emirate. The MSS will help Dubai lay the foundation for the creation of a sustainable and competitive maritime offering that will position Dubai at par with world leading maritime centers. </a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="71">Final Stage of Dubai Maritime Sector  Strategy Begins</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="72"><Comments z:Id="73" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="74" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-08-21T15:11:13</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">192</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImageFullURL z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="75" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="76" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="77" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">anchorages.stats.bunkering.updates</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="78">&lt;p&gt;The Dubai Maritime City Authority in cooperation and coordination with the Coast Guard; Dubai Police; Ministry of Environment and Water; Dubai Ports Authority and Dubai Ports World, have established authorized anchorages in Dubai waters extending to the EEZ. Ships desiring to anchor in Dubai Waters are advised to follow the attached regulations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Agents representing and supporting ships illegally anchored will be subject to sanctions and license revocation. Ships anchoring outside the approved anchorages will be subject to arrest and criminal prosecution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition DMCA is approving qualified vendors to conduct STS and Bunkering in Dubai waters. &lt;strong&gt;Only approved vendors are authorized to conduct STS and Bunkering&lt;/strong&gt;. Agents representing and supporting unauthorized STS and Bunkering operations/vendors will be subject to sanctions and license revocation. Ships conducting unauthorized STS and bunkering will be subject to arrest and criminal prosecution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to working with all concerned on enhancing the professional level of service provided by Dubai&amp;rsquo;s marine support sector. If you have any questions please feel free to contact DMCA.&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="79">Dubai Anchorages STS and Bunkering Operation Update</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="80" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-07-19T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="81" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="82">The Dubai Maritime City Authority in cooperation and coordination with the Coast Guard; Dubai Police; Ministry of Environment and Water; Dubai Ports Authority and Dubai Ports World</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="83">Dubai Anchorages STS and Bunkering Operation Update</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="84"><Comments z:Id="85" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="86" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-08-21T15:13:00</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">193</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImageFullURL z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="87" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="88" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="89" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dubai.anchorages.regulation</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="90">&lt;p&gt;This DMCA Advisory provides guidance on anchorages for vessels in Dubai waters which extends to the Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All vessels flying all flags are required to follow the regulations published in this advisory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In response to numerous queries from industry stakeholders regarding the authorization process and regulations regarding use of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Anchorage; as well as the recognized need to update the terms and conditions to ensure the safety of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Maritime Interest and the Protection of the Emirates Natural Environment and Resources the following updated regulation is effective immediately&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mariners are advised that these are regulations and shall be considered mandatory. DMCA, the Dubai Marine Police, UAE Coastguard and Criminal Investigation Department (CID) will ensure the regulations are enforced. DMCA will ensure the management and coordination of the anchorages and shall review the regulations annually with industry stakeholders and update as needed.&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="91">Dubai Anchorages Regulation</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="92" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-05-29T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="93" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="94">This DMCA Advisory provides guidance on anchorages for vessels in Dubai waters which extends to the Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ)</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="95">Dubai Anchorages Regulation</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="96"><Comments z:Id="97" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="98" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-08-21T15:15:42</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">194</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImageFullURL z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="99" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="100" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="101" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">unauthorized.anchoring.dubai.water</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="102">&lt;p&gt;Over the last eighteen months there has been a proliferation of ocean going vessels anchoring within the Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ) of the UAE and Dubai. Some of the vessels have been anchoring in approaches to vital ports such as Jebel Ali and Port Rashid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the number of large ocean ships anchoring off Dubai having increased to over sixty vessel a day we see a direct correlation between "uncontrolled anchorages" and the rise of red tides and other forms of pollution affecting the UAE fisheries, desalination efforts, and tourism industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the year the UAE Ministry of Environment and Water identified several episodes of red tides having their origin from foreign ship's ballast water discharges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The discharges coming from these illegally anchored ships have had a detrimental impact on the UAE's fishing and tourism industry. Further the risk posed by mobile point source pollution to the UAE's desalination plants was highlighted at the 2010 Desalination Water Conference sponsored by the UAE Ministry of Environment and Water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The United Nations Convention on the Law of the Sea (UNCLOS) allows for innocent passage through a nation's waters, providing that the ship complies with international law and the requirements of national and local law including environmental protection laws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mariners are hereby given notice that Dubai government will closely monitor and identify vessels that are anchoring without authorization from the DMCA.  Working with the Ministry of Environment and Water; Coast Guard; Dubai Police and other relevant UAE authorities DMCA will take appropriate action regarding the abuse of innocent passage in the waters of Dubai by unauthorized anchoring.  Drifting is not authorized and is considered analogous to anchoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In exceptional circumstances such as an emergency where anchoring cannot be avoided, mariners are advised to carefully ascertain their location, request permission from the DMCA to anchor and maintain their AIS transmission during their time in UAE waters.&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="103">Unauthorized Anchoring in Dubai Water</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="104" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-06-05T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="105" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="106">Over the last eighteen months there has been a proliferation of ocean going vessels anchoring within the Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ) of the UAE and Dubai.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="107">Unauthorized Anchoring in Dubai Water</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="108"><Comments z:Id="109" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="110" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-08-21T15:17:12</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">195</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImageFullURL z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="111" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="112" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="113" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">ship.ship.transfer.operations.regulation</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="114">&lt;p&gt;This DMCA Advisory provides guidance for vessels conducting STS operations in Dubai waters which extends to the Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All vessels flying all flags are required to follow the regulations published in this advisory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In response to numerous queries from industry stakeholders regarding the authorization process and regulations for STS operations; as well as the recognized need to update the terms and conditions to ensure the safety of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Maritime Interest and the Protection of the Emirates Natural Environment and Resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mariners are advised that these are regulations and shall be considered mandatory. DMCA, the Dubai Police, UAE Coastguard and Criminal Investigation Department (CID) will ensure the regulations are enforced.&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="115">Ship to Ship Transfer Operations Regulation</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="116" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-06-08T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="117" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="118">This DMCA Advisory provides guidance for vessels conducting STS operations in Dubai waters which extends to the Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ).</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="119">Ship to Ship Transfer Operations Regulation</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="120"><Comments z:Id="121" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="122" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-08-24T11:35:02</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">210</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="123" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/MPA Logo.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="124" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/MPA Logo.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="125" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="126" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="127" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dma.sma</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="128">&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The maritime authority in Dubai, Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) and The Maritime and Port Authority of Singapore (MPA) signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) to foster their maritime relations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Under the MOU, both MPA and the Dubai maritime authority will explore opportunities for collaboration in the area of planning and regulation of marinas and waterways.  Other possible areas of co-operation include promoting maritime environment protection as well as conducting maritime training, research, and events such as the maritime week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMCA's vision is focused on the creation of a safe and vibrant maritime environment in Dubai by the development of world-class maritime rules and regulations. Working closely with a world leading maritime authority such as the MPA will certainly help DMCA realize this vision and boost its efforts to grow a sustainable and vibrant maritime sector in Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Singapore is keen to strengthen its ties with the Middle East, a strategic region for Singapore. Beyond this MOU, MPA has worked with the United Arab Emirates in enhancing the safety of navigation and protection of marine environment in the Straits of Malacca and Singapore (SOMS) through the Co-operative Mechanism for the SOMS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"On behalf of MPA, we are pleased to be signing an MOU with DMCA which will pave the way for further collaboration between both parties. Singapore and the UAE enjoy warm and friendly bilateral relations and close cooperation in the maritime arena," says Mr Yee Cheok Hong, MPA Group Director (Policy &amp;amp; Planning).&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="129">Dubai Maritime Authority and Singapore Maritime and Ports Authority Sign MoU to Advance Maritime Relations</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="130" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2010-10-03T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="131" z:Size="2" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="132"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="133">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/MPA Logo.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>274</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="134">MPA Logo</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="135">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/MPA Logo.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="136"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="137">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/DMCA-MPA Signing/KHALEE~1.JPG</b:FullUrl><b:ID>275</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="138">Khaleej Times</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="139">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/DMCA-MPA Signing/KHALEE~1.JPG</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="140">The maritime authority in Dubai, Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) and The Maritime and Port Authority of Singapore (MPA) signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) to foster their maritime relations.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="141">Dubai Maritime Authority and Singapore Maritime and Ports Authority Sign MoU to Advance Maritime Relations</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="142"><Comments z:Id="143" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="144" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-08-24T11:35:02</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">211</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="145" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/23 Feb 2011,/GulfNews p27 (23Feb2011).jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="146" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/23 Feb 2011,/GulfNews p27 (23Feb2011).jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="147" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="148" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="149" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dma.uaeso</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="150">Dubai &lt;br /&gt;
United Arab Emirates&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The United Arabs Emirates Shipping Association, a representative body for UAE-based commercial shipping, is taking a lead position regionally and globally regarding the maritime industry&amp;rsquo;s response to climate change by supporting the efforts of the UN; IMO; and UAE Ministry of Environment and Water and DMCA in advocating for a global and open verifiable emissions trading program.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
One of the challenges that face the marine industry is reconciling their global reach with local expectations.&amp;nbsp; As of the last IMO Marine Environmental Protection Committee (MEPC) meeting there is no globally accepted or approved method or protocol to assign and include shipping in national or transnational carbon emissions reduction process. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
Ahmed Al Ghurair, President of the UAE Association stated &amp;ldquo;The UAE shipping industry recognizes that shipping, which carries 90 per cent of all world trade &amp;ndash; and 95 per cent of the UAE&amp;rsquo;s trade &amp;ndash;, must make a significant contribution in the battle to reduce mankind&amp;rsquo;s carbon emissions.&amp;rdquo; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Al Ghrair added: &amp;ldquo;The carbon cost of carrying a ton of freight by ship is 10 times less than by road &amp;ndash; and 100 times less than by air.&amp;nbsp; Shipping is by far the most carbon-friendly mode of transport.&amp;nbsp; However, because of the sheer volume of seaborne freight, shipping does produce nearly three per cent of total emissions. We need to take whatever action is needed to try to limit those emissions that have a direct daily impact on the quality of our lives, our families&amp;rsquo; health and the health of the environment.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Ships, by their very nature, move between countries (sometimes never even visiting their countries of ownership).&amp;nbsp; This raises challenging questions about the allocation of ship&amp;rsquo;s emissions.&amp;nbsp; Ships can also easily be moved between jurisdictions to avoid air emissions such as carbon regulation unless that regulation is applied regionally or internationally. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
According to Juma Mubarak CEO of Mubarak Marine &amp;ldquo;What is clear is that the industry has made significant improvements; there have been continuous improvements in fuel usage (and therefore carbon emissions) efficiency through economies of scale are vital.&amp;nbsp; We are steadily applying new engine technologies and running on economic speeds to burn more efficiently giving efficiencies to our services and value to our clients. As technologies advance and equipment improves, smaller vessel owners like us are continually able to change out old technologies and build with the most advanced methods for reducing our environmental impact. We all recognize we can do better; and we all look forward to engaging with our partners to make our industry a leader in environmental innovation. &amp;ldquo; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Mubarak operates over thirty vessels flying the UAE flag,&amp;nbsp; said he looks forward to engaging in the development of responsible standards for emissions and their measurement that brings clarity and transparency to the process giving charterers, consumers, and regulators a target while capturing the value added provided by quality performers.&lt;br /&gt;
Emarat Shipping&amp;rsquo;s Captain Misra added that any standard should emphasize the industries low carbon potential and the concept of carbon distance.&amp;nbsp; According to Misra the carbon distance takes into account the distance traveled, emissions produced and the value of the service provided.&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;Innovation in sustainable shipping will be critical to solve the climate crisis and our members are stepping up to meet the challenge. This initiative is a testament to the fact that the UAE government sees businesses as solution providers.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The UAE Shipping Association supports the IMO initiatives in creating a goal based ship design index which will encourage technical innovation for new ships. Moreover, the recent efforts by the shipping community to revisit operational parameters from slippery bottom coatings, air cushion streaming, to voluntary usage of more environmental&amp;nbsp; friendly fuels and lube oils will move the industry to further improvements.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Amer Ali Executive Director of the Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government entity in charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai , and one of the founding members of the association, said: &amp;ldquo;As the sole maritime authority in Dubai, DMCA&amp;rsquo;s strategy is based on collaboration and partnership with all the government and non-government entities operating in the maritime sector in the Emirate, because we realize and appreciate the significant role all of them play in pushing the maritime sector forward. And in line with DMCA&amp;rsquo;s vision to create a vibrant and safe maritime environment in Dubai, we will continue to work very closely with the public and private sector stakeholders to foster a better understanding of the maritime sector efforts to minimize the industry&amp;rsquo;s environmental footprint.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="151">Dubai Maritime City Authority Supports the UAE Ship Owners Association Efforts to Protect the Marine Environment </a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="152" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-02-23T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="153" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="154">The United Arabs Emirates Shipping Association, a representative body for UAE-based commercial shipping, is taking a lead position regionally and globally regarding the maritime industry’s response to climate change by supporting the efforts of the UN; IMO; and UAE Ministry of Environment and Water and DMCA in advocating for a global and open verifiable emissions trading program.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="155">Dubai Maritime City Authority Supports the UAE Ship Owners Association Efforts to Protect the Marine Environment </a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="156"><Comments z:Id="157" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="158" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-08-24T11:35:02</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">212</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="159" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/24 Apr 2011/BunkerPR.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="160" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/24 Apr 2011/BunkerPR.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="161" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="162" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="163" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.new.bunker.standard</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="164">Dubai &lt;br /&gt;
United Arab Emirates&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government entity in charge of regulating and supervising&amp;nbsp; all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, hosted the first of three UAE Bunker Standard workshops recently in support of the&amp;nbsp; UAE&amp;nbsp; Initiative to develop a 21st century&amp;nbsp; bunker standard.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The goal of the negotiated regulation is to incorporate industry best practices and standards to benefit the entire marine industry.&amp;nbsp; The Initiative is a joint working effort of the Ministry of Environment and Water, NTA, and the Emirate&amp;rsquo;s local Marine Regulatory Authorities. Participants included Emirate&amp;rsquo;s Marine Regulatory representatives; bunker suppliers, the UAE Shipping Association, ship-owners, operators, charterers, bunker craft operators, bunker testing labs and bunker surveyors.&lt;br /&gt;
DMCA is working closely with these partners to help ensure that the new standard is designed in such a manner that the UAE will continue to lead the&amp;nbsp; industry through active engagement, practical solutions, and responsible regulations and policies.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The UAE, , is the world&amp;rsquo;s second largest bunkering port with an estimated amount of 12 million&amp;nbsp; metric tons lifted annually.&amp;nbsp; The Initiative has several objectives that are aligned with the IMO&amp;rsquo;s MARPOL requirements including meeting the 3.5% sulfur content for bunkers starting from 1 Jan 2012.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;
Other objectives include creating a concise chain of custody control procedures that are fair to all parties;&amp;nbsp; to ensure the highest quality of bunker fuel is available for delivery; that quality fuel is assigned a value rating based upon parameters designed to ensure the least amount of CO2 production per quantity of fuel consumed per nautical mile traveled; ensuring that the quantity delivered is consistently accurate; that the bunkers are delivered safely and in an environmentally sustainable manner. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The objectives look to minimize bunkering disputes; provide annual reporting goals for the industry based on agreed upon Key Performance Indicators, and establish a dispute resolution process that benefits operations and the UAE.</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="165">Dubai Maritime City Authority Hosts a Workshop to Discuss Establishment of a New UAE Bunker Standard</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="166" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-04-24T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="167" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="168">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government entity in charge of regulating and supervising  all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, hosted the first of three UAE Bunker Standard workshops recently in support of the  UAE  Initiative to develop a 21st century  bunker standard.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="169">Dubai Maritime City Authority Hosts a Workshop to Discuss Establishment of a New UAE Bunker Standard</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="170"><Comments z:Id="171" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="172" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2011-08-24T11:35:02</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">213</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="173" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageAr/4 July 2011/Picture4july2011.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="174" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageAr/4 July 2011/Picture4july2011.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="175" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="176" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="177" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.facilitates.oil.tanker.crew.member</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="178">&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the lead maritime government entity charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced that it has successfully facilitated the safe repatriation of crew members of one of the non-operational Korean oil tankers stranded in Dubai's waters. In coordination with the Dubai Port Police, and other concerned authorities, DMCA led a team that boarded Samho DREAM to conduct safety and health inspections, which eventually led to the Master of the DREAM asking that all of the DREAM's personnel be allowed ashore until the ship had power and water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The DREAM is one of three ship's owned by the now bankrupt SAMHO Shipping in Dubai's anchorages. SAMHO Shipping had a rough 2010 and 2011, and commercial daily rates for VLCC's tumbling to unprecedented lows. The bankruptcy proceedings in Korea has left the crews in desperate condition for several weeks with the last few seeing no potable water and no power for refrigeration of food, cooking, communications, or navigation. The crew of the DREAM were only able to communicate to ships anchored nearby through the portable VHF radios on the lifeboats, which have limited range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Khalid Meftah, Director of Maritime Corporate Development at Dubai Maritime City Authority, said: "Dubai Maritime City Authority has coordinated with various government agencies as well as the shipping company's representative and the flag state representative in implementing an immediate interim safety plan. The crew were already in an adverse condition with a few reporting weight loss, and dizziness, we had to act swiftly for them to be brought ashore and cared for in line with Dubai's safety and territorial regulations."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It was critically important to maintain a high level of transparency to keep all parties properly informed and ensure that the entire operation was conducted in line with the standards and regulations implemented by Dubai Government. The successful implementation of the safety plan for the ship and the speedy rescue and repatriation of the crew certainly underlines the full capabilities of DMCA to effectively coordinate with the Dubai Police as well as international authorities and private sector stakeholders.," added Meftah.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMCA representative, Captain Abdullah Al Hayyas who led the team that inspected the ship, confirmed the harsh conditions of the sailors and also implemented several on board safety measures. He recommended that immediate medical and other humanitarian assistance must be given to the crew. One of Captain Al Hayyas's findings was the ship's Master had not had any contact with the owners for over a week due to the company shutting off access to the internet and satellite phone."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMCA established communication with the ship owners, who duly repatriated the crew to their respective home countries and are now working closely with DMCA to settle other legal obligations. DMCA has also coordinated with Dubai Police to safeguard the ships while they are in Dubai's territory.&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="179">Dubai Maritime City Authority facilitates successful rescue, repatriation of troubled crew members of stranded oil tankers</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="180" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-07-04T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Id="181">Data/Images/NewsImageAr/4 July 2011/Picture4july2011.jpg</a:NewsThumbnail><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="182" z:Size="4" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="183"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="184">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageAr/4 July 2011/Picture4july2011.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>871</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="185">DMCA with Stranded Sailors</b:Title><b:Url z:Ref="181" i:nil="true"/></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="186"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="187">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/4 July 2011/DMCA - SAMHO Shipping news clips-1.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>872</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="188">Shipping news 1 - 4/7/2011</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="189">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/4 July 2011/DMCA - SAMHO Shipping news clips-1.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="190"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="191">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/4 July 2011/DMCA - SAMHO Shipping news clips-2.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>873</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="192">Shipping news 2 - 4/7/2011</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="193">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/4 July 2011/DMCA - SAMHO Shipping news clips-2.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="194"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="195">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/4 July 2011/DMCA - SAMHO Shipping news clips-3.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>874</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="196">Shipping news 3 - 4/7/2011</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="197">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/4 July 2011/DMCA - SAMHO Shipping news clips-3.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="198">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the lead maritime government entity charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced that it has successfully facilitated the safe repatriation of crew members of one of the non-operational Korean oil tankers stranded in Dubai's waters. In coordination with the Dubai Port Police, and other concerned authorities, DMCA led a team that boarded Samho DREAM to conduct safety and health inspections, which eventually led to the Master of the DREAM asking that all of the DREAM's personnel be allowed ashore until the ship had power and water.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="199">Dubai Maritime City Authority facilitates successful rescue, repatriation of troubled crew members of stranded oil tankers</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="200"><Comments z:Id="201" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="202" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-02-26T16:26:42</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">242</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImageFullURL z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="203" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="204" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="205" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.boat.show</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="206">Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government entity in-charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced its support to the Dubai International Boat Show 2012, which will take place from March 13 to 17, 2012, at the Dubai International Marine Club, Mina Seyahi. As a specialized pavilion exhibitor, DMCA aims to raise awareness on the role of the maritime authority in supporting the development of a safe and highly developed maritime sector in Dubai.&lt;br /&gt;
DMCA&amp;rsquo;s pavilion will provide a presentation of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s best practices in boating, and introduce various safety procedures for marine applications that are being enforced by the maritime authority. Provisions concerning the boating community in the newly unveiled Strategic Plan for developing Dubai&amp;rsquo;s maritime sector will also be presented by DMCA, as well as those that focus on the development and regulation of the maritime sector, which ultimately aim to enhance Dubai&amp;rsquo;s position as a leading destination in the international maritime industry.&lt;br /&gt;
DMCA will also conduct presentations about the regulations that have been introduced to maintain the high levels of safety and ensure environmental protection in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s waters, along with best international practices adopted by the emirate in line with Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Maritime Strategic Plan.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The authority will also unveil new awareness campaigns during the Boat Show, targeting recreational boating enthusiasts in Dubai. These initiatives are being developed by the maritime authority in collaboration with various industry-related organisations as well as the Dubai Port Police. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
Amer Ali, Executive Director of DMCA, said: &amp;ldquo;Dubai International Boat Show is one of the most prestigious and largest networking events for stakeholders in the regional recreational boating and yachting industry, presenting an excellent platform to discuss and create greater awareness about DMCA&amp;rsquo;s ongoing initiatives and long-term strategic plans. Moreover, Dubai is increasingly becoming the region&amp;rsquo;s leading maritime hub and there is certainly a growing interest in DMCA&amp;rsquo;s role as the regulating and supervising entity in the emirate&amp;rsquo;s boating sector. Dubai International Boat Show therefore serves as an ideal venue for DMCA to engage in meaningful discussions and interaction with stakeholders of the region&amp;rsquo;s boating industry about key maritime issues and Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Maritime Strategic Plan.&amp;rdquo;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="207">DMCA supports Dubai International Boat Show 2012 as specialized pavilion exhibitor</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="208" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-01-29T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="209" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="210">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government entity in-charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced its support to the Dubai International Boat Show 2012, which will take place from March 13 to 17, 2012, at the Dubai International Marine Club, Mina Seyahi. As a specialized pavilion exhibitor, DMCA aims to raise awareness on the role of the maritime authority in supporting the development of a safe and highly developed maritime sector in Dubai.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="211">DMCA supports Dubai International Boat Show 2012 as specialized pavilion exhibitor</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="212"><Comments z:Id="213" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="214" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-02-26T16:29:39</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">243</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="215" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageAr/1 Feb 2012/EnMedia.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="216" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageAr/1 Feb 2012/EnMedia.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="217" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="218" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="219" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">cruise.ship.drill</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="220">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the maritime government entity charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced the establishment of a cruise ship task force in line with its continued efforts to ensure the safety of cruise ships arriving in Dubai and to reinforce Dubai&amp;rsquo;s preparedness to deal with potential maritime accidents. The cruise ship task force has been established in collaboration with Dubai Tourism &amp;amp; Commerce Marketing (DTCM).&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
DMCA further revealed that it is intensifying maritime inspections to ensure that cruise ships comply with maritime standards and to create awareness among ship owners and cruise operators about the need to improve the performance of cruise ships according to best practices in the industry.&lt;br /&gt;
Hamad bin Mejren, DTCM Executive Director for Business Tourism, said: &amp;ldquo;Dubai is keen to adopt best practices related to the safety of cruise ships, in line with international standards and norms. DTCM has partnered with DMCA as part of our commitment to ensure that cruise trips from Dubai will set a global standard in terms of safety and readiness to handle various eventualities, as well as to provide world-class logistical and technical support to the cruise ships.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
DMCA is cooperating with the Ports Police, Civil Defense, Dubai Ports Security, Customs Security and Free Zones Security, ship agencies, DP World and the National Authority for the Management of Emergencies and Crises to strictly enforce the maritime regulations. Moreover, DMCA has ordered all cruise ships to carry out evacuation exercises before leaving Dubai to ensure that the crew is fully prepared in case of accidents.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Safety is very important in the cruise ship industry. For this reason, DMCA constantly works to review and update local laws, to ensure compliance and adherence to best practices and international standards. It is important that all industry stakeholders must work as a team to achieve our goal of putting Dubai on the global maritime map as a safe tourist destination, while enhancing Dubai&amp;rsquo;s preparedness to face any eventuality,&amp;rdquo; said Ali Al Daboos, Executive Director of DMCA.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Other key measures adopted by DMCA include gauging incident command system maritime domain awareness of stakeholders, compiling of cruise sector and shore side response Gap Analysis; and discussing with DMCA partners the Maritime Strategy Work Shops regarding the cruise sector. DMCA also conducts inspections before authorizing ships to sail to check the readiness of the crew and their commitment to emergency procedures.</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="221">Dubai Maritime City Authority adopts best practices to increase safety and security of cruise ships</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="222" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-02-01T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Id="223">Data/Images/NewsImageAr/1 Feb 2012/OnboardCruiseShip.jpg</a:NewsThumbnail><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="224" z:Size="2" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="225"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="226">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageAr/1 Feb 2012/EnMedia.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>777</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="227">Media</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="228">Data/Images/NewsImageAr/1 Feb 2012/EnMedia.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="229"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="230">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageAr/1 Feb 2012/OnboardCruiseShip.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>778</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="231">Onboard Cruise Ship</b:Title><b:Url z:Ref="223" i:nil="true"/></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="232">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the maritime government entity charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced the establishment of a cruise ship task force in line with its continued efforts to ensure the safety of cruise ships arriving in Dubai and to reinforce Dubai’s preparedness to deal with potential maritime accidents. The cruise ship task force has been established in collaboration with Dubai Tourism &amp; Commerce Marketing (DTCM).</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="233">Dubai Maritime City Authority adopts best practices to increase safety and security of cruise ships</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="234"><Comments z:Id="235" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="236" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-03-21T13:37:58</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">249</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImageFullURL z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="237" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="238" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="239" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.dibs.overall.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="240">Dubai, UAE: As part of its ongoing efforts to enhance supervision of maritime activities and consolidate Dubai's position as a pioneer in excellence, innovation and sustainability in the regional and international maritime industry, Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government entity in-charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has completed extensive preparations for its participation at the Dubai International Boat Show 2012, to be held at the Dubai International Marine Club, Mina Seyahi, from March 13 to 17.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
DMCA will have an exclusive pavilion at the Dubai International Boat Show as it aims to create greater awareness about best practices and standards of maritime safety among users and operators of different marine crafts and recreational boats in Dubai.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The maritime authority will also distribute copies of a special booklet titled &amp;ldquo;Safety and Security Guidelines for Users of Jet Skis&amp;rdquo;, as part of continuing efforts to develop services, regulations and guidelines that aim to further strengthen the level of safety and help improve the maritime environment in Dubai, while enhancing the emirate&amp;rsquo;s position as a premier international maritime hub. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Furthermore, the initiative complements the continuing efforts of DMCA to raise awareness in society about the importance of using safety devices when handling jet skis and other water crafts, emphasizing the need to abide by safety instructions and laws, be familiar with the rules of usage, traffic, slip way places, areas of marine activities, and taking preventive measures to avoid accidents.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Amer Ali, Executive Director of DMCA, said: &amp;ldquo;We always focus on raising public awareness for the safety of practitioners of different marine sports by launching awareness campaigns, participating in marine industry events and strengthening cooperation and coordination between various stakeholders in the Emirate. Promoting safety standards is of paramount importance for us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Ali added: &amp;ldquo;We are delighted to participate in Dubai International Boat Show, which serves as an ideal networking platform with all regional and international stakeholders and decision makers within the leisure boat and yacht sector. It allows us to discuss key maritime issues related to recreational boating. During the event we will also unveil our strategic plans that aim to create a safe and sustainable maritime environment that reinforces Dubai&amp;rsquo;s position as a leader in maritime excellence and development. We look forward to promoting safety procedures and various ways of avoiding marine accidents by following early warnings and sea guidelines.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="241">Dubai Maritime City Authority Promotes Best Practices of Maritime Craft Usages at Dubai International Boat Show 2012</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="242" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-03-12T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="243" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="244">As part of its ongoing efforts to enhance supervision of maritime activities and consolidate Dubai's position as a pioneer in excellence, innovation and sustainability in the regional and international maritime industry, Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government entity in-charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has completed extensive preparations for its participation at the Dubai International Boat Show 2012, to be held at the Dubai International Marine Club, Mina Seyahi, from March 13 to 17.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="245">Dubai Maritime City Authority Promotes Best Practices of Maritime Craft Usages at Dubai International Boat Show 2012</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="246"><Comments z:Id="247" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="248" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-03-21T13:51:47</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">250</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImageFullURL z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="249" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="250" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="251" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.footfall.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="252">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government entity in-charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has received an enthusiastic response from visitors during its first participation at the Dubai International Boat Show. The event provided an excellent platform to better understand DMCA&amp;rsquo;s scope of work and role in raising greater awareness about marine best practices that support the development of a safe and vibrant&amp;nbsp; maritime sector in Dubai.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The DMCA pavilion attracted a wide range of visitors from the boating industry leaders in the Middle East to water sports fans. The visitors were introduced to key services provided by the authority, while helping boating enthusiasts and maritime professionals get acquainted with many issues regarding safe operations of marine crafts, such as the procedures of maneuvering and maritime traffic. DMCA also discussed slipways and sports activities, safety equipment, maritime environment among others. Representatives from DMCA were present at the pavilion to interact with visitors and answer their questions regarding maritime activities in Dubai.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The visitors, who included decision makers from the private and public sectors, industry leaders and water sports enthusiasts, commended the DMCA for its participation in the boat show, as it added a unique dimension to the event by serving as a platform to raise awareness about the importance of using safety equipment and complying with maritime laws and regulations. Visitors further lauded DMCA for its efforts to draw greater attention to various safety measures and in reducing maritime accidents that are often the result of personal negligence or failure to follow warning signs at sea.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Amer Ali, CEO, Dubai Maritime City Authority, expressed his delight with the positive response they received at the 20th edition of Dubai International Boat Show, which demonstrates DMCA&amp;rsquo;s vital role in the maritime industry and its support to the Dubai Government&amp;rsquo;s vision of developing the maritime sector according to the highest international standards. Ali emphasized the importance of participating in such an event to be able to communicate with decision makers, and water sports enthusiasts and professionals. It also allows them to reach out to a much larger segment of the society to enhance awareness about the latest measures and best practices that guarantee maritime safety, particularly during various water sports events. The participation served as an integral part of DMCA&amp;rsquo;s mission to create an integrated maritime environment and a and sustainable maritime industry under the highest standards of safety, excellence and leadership.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Ali added: &amp;ldquo;The great success achieved during the event drives us to further intensify our efforts and launch more initiatives that would help promote best practices and subsequently raise the bar of maritime excellence at the local, regional and international levels.&amp;rdquo;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="253">DMCA receives enthusiastic response from visitors at Dubai International Boat Show</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="254" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-03-13T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="255" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="256">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government entity in-charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has received an enthusiastic response from visitors during its first participation at the Dubai International Boat Show. The event provided an excellent platform to better understand DMCA’s scope of work and role in raising greater awareness about marine best practices that support the development of a safe and vibrant  maritime sector in Dubai.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="257">DMCA receives enthusiastic response from visitors at Dubai International Boat Show</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="258"><Comments z:Id="259" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="260" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-03-22T10:56:02</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">252</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="261" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageAr/2 Feb 2011/DMADWTC.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="262" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageAr/2 Feb 2011/DMADWTC.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="263" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="264" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="265" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dma.dwtc.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="266">Dubai &lt;br /&gt;
United Arab Emirates&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Dubai Maritime City Authority, the government entity in charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, today signed a mutual cooperation agreement with Dubai World Trade Centre as part of its ongoing efforts to support the region&amp;rsquo;s leading maritime event &amp;ndash; the Dubai International Boat Show, which will be held at the Dubai International Marine Club &amp;ndash; Mina Seyahi from 1 &amp;ndash; 5 March 2011.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Year after year, Dubai International Boat Show renews its dedication to position Dubai as the number one destination for all leisure marine sectors, offering unparalleled products and services. At the 2010 event, 23,000 buyers, trade professional and enthusiasts from 76 countries visited the show, which included more than 700 industry leading exhibitors from 40 countries, recording multi-million dollar onsite sales.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
With US$35 billion dollars worth of marina developments planned over the next three years, the GCC is one of the most attractive markets in the industry, and this year&amp;rsquo;s show is expecting to welcome more high profile international exhibitors than ever before. A sentiment reflected by the prestigious country pavilions taking part, including Australia, USA, Turkey, France and Italy.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Helal Saeed Almarri, CEO, Dubai World Trade Centre, organiser of the event, said: &amp;ldquo;The Dubai International Boat Show is the largest, longest running and most successful leisure marine event in the region. For nearly two decades, the show has attracted an unrivalled calibre of visitors and exhibitors, and helped to drive a regional market which is increasingly becoming the focus of global industry attention.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Dubai Maritime City Authority is the optimal partner to drive even higher levels of awareness and excellence on safety, security and quality in the region&amp;rsquo;s maritime sector in general, and in recreational boating in particular.&amp;nbsp; The Maritime Authority plays an active role in driving global industry standards, which fully supports the rapidly growing and sustainable maritime environment in Dubai.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The 2011 edition of the show features some of the most established leisure marine organisations and superyacht shipyards in the world. International industry leaders such as Azimut, Hatteras, Princess Yachts, Sunseeker and Westport and SYBass members Amels, Benetti, Burger Boat Company, Fincantieri, Heesen Yachts, L&amp;uuml;rssen Yachts, Oceanco, Sanlorenzo and Trinity Yachts that will line up alongside the exclusive locally-built brands including Al Shaali Marine, Gulf Craft and Majesty.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The Marina Display area, the largest on-water display in the Middle East, the area also includes an unrivalled range of power boats, sailing boats, sports and speed boats &amp;ndash; and the Enhanced Superyacht Boulevard, exclusively reserved for luxurious super yachts of 25 metres and above.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Dubai Maritime City Authority&amp;rsquo;s strategy is based on collaboration and partnership with all the government and non-government entities operating in the maritime sector in Dubai, because we realize and appreciate the significant role all of them play in pushing the maritime sector forward. Our partnership with Dubai International Boat Show &amp;ndash; the event of excellence in the region - is especially important as it will help us to lend greater support and value to the growing and highly important sector of recreational boating in Dubai.&amp;rdquo; said Amer Ali, the Executive Director of Dubai Maritime Authority. &lt;br /&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="267">Dubai Maritime City Authority Partners with  Dubai International Boat Show 2011 </a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="268" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-02-02T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Id="269">Data/Images/NewsImageAr/2 Feb 2011/DMADWTC.jpg</a:NewsThumbnail><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="270" z:Size="2" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="271"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="272">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageAr/2 Feb 2011/DMADWTC.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>844</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="273">Helal Saeed Almarri with Amer Ali</b:Title><b:Url z:Ref="269" i:nil="true"/></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="274"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="275">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/2 Feb 2011,/KhaleejTimes p47 (3Feb2011) copy.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>845</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="276">Khaleej Times - 2/2/2011</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="277">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/2 Feb 2011,/KhaleejTimes p47 (3Feb2011) copy.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="278">Dubai Maritime City Authority, the government entity in charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, today signed a mutual cooperation agreement with Dubai World Trade Centre as part of its ongoing efforts to support the region’s leading maritime event – the Dubai International Boat Show, which will be held at the Dubai International Marine Club – Mina Seyahi from 1 – 5 March 2011.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="279">Dubai Maritime City Authority Partners with  Dubai International Boat Show 2011 </a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="280"><Comments z:Id="281" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="282" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-03-22T11:59:36</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">253</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="283" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageAr/23 Aug 2011/samhodream.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="284" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageAr/23 Aug 2011/samhodream.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="285" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="286" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="287" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.jasper</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="288">Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the lead maritime government entity charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced, together with&amp;nbsp; the Dubai Port Police, that the successful repatriation of 21 crew members of the SAMHO JASPER, a Korean tanker that was idled in Dubai waters, was completed last week.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
SAMHO JASPER, which has been renamed GOLDEN LAKE, is now out of Dubai waters. DMCA successfully coordinated with the Port Police, the Harbor Master's office, Korean Consulate and the Korean owners and operators to safely manage the offshore situation and ensure a swift resolution of the outstanding issues.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The crew members, who were from Indonesia and Myanmar, had endured several months without pay and at times with limited supply of water and power, relying on DMCA and the Dubai government to intervene on their behalf with healthcare and logistics support. DMCA further confirmed that two other stranded tankers &amp;ndash; SAMHO DREAM and SAMHO CROWN, which are also owned by the same Korean shipping company &amp;ndash; are being monitored and remain in a warm lay up status. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
SAMHO Shipping had filed for bankruptcy in Korea and is now emerging from the reorganization.&amp;nbsp; SAMHO representatives flew into Dubai this past week from Korea to meet with DMCA to discuss how best to reactivate the tankers and resolve all outstanding issues.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
DMCA with the support of the DM government successfully negotiated with the concerned parties to ensure that the crew members were properly compensated for back pay before they were repatriated, while also ensuring payment to local service providers.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
DMCA successfully facilitated negotiations with the parties involved that allowed the maritime authority to work out a solution without having to resort to litigation that could potentially take years to resolve. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The successful resolution of this matter underlines the commitment of Dubai Government to protect the interest of stakeholders in the maritime sector and to support the sustainable growth of the industry.</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="289">Dubai Maritime City Authority completes repatriation of 21 crew members of stranded Korean oil tanker</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="290" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2011-08-23T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="291" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="292">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the lead maritime government entity charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced, together with  the Dubai Port Police, that the successful repatriation of 21 crew members of the SAMHO JASPER, a Korean tanker that was idled in Dubai waters, was completed last week.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="293">Dubai Maritime City Authority completes repatriation of 21 crew members of stranded Korean oil tanker</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="294"><Comments z:Id="295" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="296" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-03-25T10:38:13</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">255</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="297" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/3 Oct 2010,/KhaleejTimes p22 (4 Oct2010).jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="298" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/3 Oct 2010,/KhaleejTimes p22 (4 Oct2010).jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="299" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="300" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="301" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.mpa.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="302">Dubai, United Arab Emirates &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The maritime authority in Dubai, Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) and The Maritime and Port Authority of Singapore (MPA) signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) to foster their maritime relations. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Under the MOU, both MPA and the Dubai maritime authority will explore opportunities for collaboration in the area of planning and regulation of marinas and waterways.&amp;nbsp; Other possible areas of co-operation include promoting maritime environment protection as well as conducting maritime training, research, and events such as the maritime week.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
DMCA&amp;rsquo;s vision is focused on the creation of a safe and vibrant maritime environment in Dubai by the development of world-class maritime rules and regulations. Working closely with a world leading maritime authority such as the MPA will certainly help DMCA realize this vision and boost its efforts to grow a sustainable and vibrant maritime sector in Dubai.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Singapore is keen to strengthen its ties with the Middle East, a strategic region for Singapore.&amp;nbsp; Beyond this MOU, MPA has worked with the United Arab Emirates in enhancing the safety of navigation and protection of marine environment in the Straits of Malacca and Singapore (SOMS) through the Co-operative Mechanism for the SOMS. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ldquo;On behalf of MPA, we are pleased to be signing an MOU with DMCA which will pave the way for further collaboration between both parties. Singapore and the UAE enjoy warm and friendly bilateral relations and close cooperation in the maritime arena,&amp;rdquo; says Mr Yee Cheok Hong, MPA Group Director (Policy &amp;amp; Planning).</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="303">Dubai Maritime Authority and Singapore Maritime and Ports Authority Sign MoU to Advance Maritime Relations</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="304" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2010-10-03T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="305" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="306">The maritime authority in Dubai, Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) and The Maritime and Port Authority of Singapore (MPA) signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) to foster their maritime relations. </a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="307">Dubai Maritime Authority and Singapore Maritime and Ports Authority Sign MoU to Advance Maritime Relations</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="308"><Comments z:Id="309" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="310" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-06-12T09:52:46</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">257</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="311" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/11 June 2012/DMCAUSAVisit.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="312" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/11 June 2012/DMCAUSAVisit.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="313" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="314" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="315" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmcausavisit</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="316">Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A high-level delegation comprising senior officials from Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government authority in charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai and the Department of Transport, Abu Dhabi, recently concluded a visit to the United States of America where they met different marine entities in California to discuss various aspects of maritime environment and pollution. The DMCA team was headed by Amer Ali, CEO of Dubai Maritime City Authority, while Majed Al Shamsi, represented the Department of Transport.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The delegation first met the California Air Resources Board (CARB), which has been responsible for developing a comprehensive body of regulation regarding ocean going vessels over the last two decades. DMCA officials discussed topics such as ship emissions, and innovative approaches to mitigate air pollution by ships in ports such as providing shore-side electrical power to the ship at berth while its main and auxiliary engines are turned off.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The team&amp;rsquo;s US visit also featured meetings with the Department of Boating &amp;amp; Waterways - California&amp;rsquo;s regulator for boat registration, water ways designation, and boating safety education &amp;ndash; and representatives from the Marine Invasive Species Program. The program was initiated by the California Lands Commission to limit evasive species introductions to the California coast from ocean going vessels arriving from far foreign trips. The DMCA officials were given an overview of the measures adopted by the Lands Commission to limit the introduction of potentially harmful species to the California coast.&lt;br /&gt;
Amer Ali, CEO of Dubai Maritime City Authority, said, &amp;ldquo;This visit to the United States is in line with DMCA&amp;rsquo;s strategy of adopting the best international practices in all maritime-related aspects, especially environmental protection. For the last several decades the state of California has been pioneering efforts to ensure that commercial shipping operations have minimal impact on the marine environment. This visit allowed us to exchange knowledge, best practices and experiences with our counterparts in California, which will go a long way in our efforts to promote and protect the marine environment in the UAE and the country&amp;rsquo;s vital marine facilities.&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The delegation concluded their visit with a meeting with Chris Lytle, Director of Port of Long Beach, a multi-use green port and a pioneer port for container ships. Lytle briefed the DMCA team about various topics such as the innovative approach to scheduling of trucks to allow for the least amount of emissions and traffic congestion.</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="317">DMCA discusses maritime environment protection best practices with California marine authorities</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="318" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-06-11T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="319" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="320">A high-level delegation comprising senior officials from Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government authority in charge of regulating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai and the Department of Transport, Abu Dhabi, recently concluded a visit to the United States of America where they met different marine entities in California to discuss various aspects of maritime environment and pollution.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="321">DMCA discusses maritime environment protection best practices with California marine authorities</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="322"><Comments z:Id="323" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="324" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-07-03T11:09:11</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">260</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="325" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/3 July 2012/DPW DMCA MW.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="326" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/3 July 2012/DPW DMCA MW.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="327" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="328" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="329" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.dmw.dpw.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="330">Dubai, United Arab Emirates &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) today announced it is launching the first ever Dubai Maritime Week, to be held in November this year.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In collaboration with several strategic partners from Dubai Government, DMCA will organize a number of maritime industry-related activities and events, including conferences, discussion panels and forums, as well as public-oriented activities to celebrate Dubai&amp;rsquo;s maritime heritage. DMCA will also organize a series of programs at the Dubai Maritime Week to raise awareness about the urgent need to support the expansion and growth of the maritime industry in Dubai. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The week coincides with the Seatrade Middle East Maritime 2012 Exhibition, Awards and Conference, which is expected to attract hundreds of global equipment suppliers, modern technology providers and service providers to Dubai. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Dubai-headquartered global port operator DP World has welcomed the initiative. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
H.E. Sultan Ahmed Bin Sulayem, Chairman, DP World said:&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Dubai has been a maritime hub for generations, and is the centre for trade for a region of some 2 billion people across the GCC, the Subcontinent and east Africa, with DP World&amp;rsquo;s Jebel Ali port at the heart of that activity.&amp;nbsp; The Dubai Maritime Week 2012 is an exciting initiative that will bring together the key players in the industry to share ideas and best practice and explore business opportunities.&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Mohammed Sharaf, CEO, DP World, said: &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ldquo;This event provides an interactive platform to build and develop strategic relations, gathering all industry professionals, associations, experts, suppliers and ship owners in the region. We at DP World are delighted to support this first-of-its-kind event in Dubai.&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Amer Ali, CEO, Dubai Maritime City Authority said: &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ldquo;We appreciate the support of DP World for the Dubai Maritime Week 2012, which we have developed to enhance the quality of maritime services available in Dubai and the wider region, and ultimately promote the growth of the maritime industry in Dubai.&amp;rdquo;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="331">DMCA Launches ‘Dubai Maritime Week 2012’ DP World welcomes and supports the initiative</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="332" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-07-03T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="333" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="334">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) today announced it is launching the first ever Dubai Maritime Week, to be held in November this year.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="335">DMCA Launches ‘Dubai Maritime Week 2012’ DP World welcomes and supports the initiative</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="336"><Comments z:Id="337" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="338" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">administrator</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-08-29T08:58:41</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">268</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="339" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/28 Aug 2012/AlZaabiAndAmerAli.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="340" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/28 Aug 2012/AlZaabiAndAmerAli.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="341" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="342" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="343" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">nta.supports.dmw.2012.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="344">Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The National Transport Authority (NTA) has announced its full support for the first-ever Dubai Maritime Week 2012, to be held in November 2012 in Dubai. The NTA&amp;rsquo;s support highlights the critical role of the event in strengthening the UAE&amp;rsquo;s position as a regional and global trade and economic hub, and in showcasing the country&amp;rsquo;s ability to host prestigious international conferences and events.&lt;br /&gt;
H.E. Salem Al Zaabi, Acting Director-General of the National Transport Authority: &amp;ldquo;Our support for the Dubai Maritime Week 2012 is in line with our belief in its importance and positive impact on the maritime sector in the UAE. This event validates the UAE&amp;rsquo;s ability to host top events in the maritime industry and to keep pace with rapid developments at all levels.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;
In collaboration with strategic partners from Dubai Government, Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) will organize a number of maritime industry-related activities and events such as conferences, panel discussions and forums, as well as public-oriented activities to celebrate Dubai&amp;rsquo;s maritime heritage. DMCA will also organize various programs during the Dubai Maritime Week to raise awareness about the urgent need to support the expansion and growth of the maritime industry in Dubai.&lt;br /&gt;
Al Zaabi added: &amp;ldquo;This event serves as an interactive platform dedicated to building and strengthening strategic relationships, as it brings together under one roof all professionals, associations, experts, suppliers in the maritime sector and ship owners in the region. We at the National Transport Authority are pleased to support this important and first-of-its-kind event in Dubai.&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The Dubai Maritime Week 2012 is being organized through the close cooperation between Dubai Maritime City Authority and Seatrade. The upcoming Seatrade Middle East Maritime Exhibition &amp;amp; Conference 2012 &amp;ndash; which will be part of Dubai Maritime Week 2012 - will host a number of international companies including suppliers of equipment, modern technologies and specialized services. On the sidelines of these events, DMCA, in collaboration with its strategic allies, will hold a number of activities and special events, in addition to a series of programs aimed at increasing awareness about the important role of the maritime sector in the emirate.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;Amer Ali, CEO, Dubai Maritime City Authority said: &amp;ldquo;It is with great honor and pride that we receive the support of the National Transport Authority. This cooperation is the result of our shared vision and the continuing efforts by both parties to improve the standards of maritime services and to develop the maritime sector in Dubai and the UAE in general. We are proud and happy to receive this support.&amp;rdquo;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="345">National Transport Authority supports Dubai Maritime Week 2012</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="346" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-08-28T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Id="347">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/28 Aug 2012/AlZaabiAndAmerAli.jpg</a:NewsThumbnail><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="348" z:Size="2" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="349"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="350">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/28 Aug 2012/AlZaabiAndAmerAli.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>907</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="351">AlZaabi And Amer Ali</b:Title><b:Url z:Ref="347" i:nil="true"/></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="352"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="353">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/28 Aug 2012/GulfNews p5 (28 Aug 2012).jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>908</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="354">Gulf News - 28/8/2012</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="355">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/28 Aug 2012/GulfNews p5 (28 Aug 2012).jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="356">The National Transport Authority (NTA) has announced its full support for the first-ever Dubai Maritime Week 2012, to be held in November 2012 in Dubai. The NTA’s support highlights the critical role of the event in strengthening the UAE’s position as a regional and global trade and economic hub, and in showcasing the country’s ability to host prestigious international conferences and events.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="357">National Transport Authority supports Dubai Maritime Week 2012</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="358"><Comments z:Id="359" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="360" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">EmanCSR</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-10-15T13:41:21</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">274</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="361" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/DMCA Taskforce.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="362" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/DMCA Taskforce.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="363" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="364" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="365" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.taskforce.2012.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="366">&lt;p&gt;DMCA hosts Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force meeting to discuss priorities for new cruise season&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Safety and environmental aspects key focus areas for 2012/13&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government authority charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has revealed that the Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force met with the representatives from the cruise industry to discuss the priorities for the 2012/13 cruise season. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two new areas of focus for the upcoming cruise season are safety (fire safety and areas of high risk) and environmental aspects. The high risk areas were determined after reviewing the 20-year historical record of the cruise industry. On the other hand, to ensure that the environmental aspects of cruise ships are adequately managed, DMCA will coordinate with Dubai Municipality, UAE Ministry of Environment and Water, and the Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM) to collect and verify the various environmental efforts being undertaken by cruise ships. The cruise ship that sets the highest leadership and performance standards, and demonstrates utmost care and environmental responsibility will be rewarded with the newly launched annual environmental award. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amer Ali, CEO, Dubai Maritime City Authority, said: &amp;ldquo;The overriding goal of the Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force is to actively identify a range of measures to improve the safety of passengers, crew and the ports. DMCA will continue to work closely with the Task Force and all stakeholders of the cruise industry to reaffirm the reputation of Dubai and the rest of the UAE as one of the best international cruise destinations that places the highest emphasis on safety and quality standards.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, the Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force hosted the first cruise sector mass casualty table top exercise and drill. The Task Force, focused on how best to organize and respond to a multiple casualty event aboard a cruise ship in port or in near coastal waters, given that such a situation would require a significant amount of communication and coordination across public and private sector operations. The tabletop exercise, taken from real-life occurrences, simulated multiple casualties aboard a cruise ship outside of Port Rashid in Dubai.&lt;br /&gt;
The Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force was established in September of 2011 by the DTCM and DMCA to help ensure the safety of cruise ships arriving in Dubai and to reinforce Dubai&amp;rsquo;s preparedness to deal with potential maritime accidents. The Task Force&amp;rsquo;s findings for the 2011/12 season have already made a significant positive impact on the way the cruise sector operates in UAE waters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Task Force will next meet with officials from other emirates and federal government authorities to report the recent progress and the voyage plan for the future. &lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="367">DMCA hosts Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force meeting to discuss priorities for new cruise season   </a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="368" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-09-26T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Id="369">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/DMCA Taskforce.jpg</a:NewsThumbnail><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="370" z:Size="4" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="371"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="372">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/Al Bayan p8 (26 Sep 2012).jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>933</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="373">Al Bayan 26/9/2012</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="374">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/Al Bayan p8 (26 Sep 2012).jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="375"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="376">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/Al Khaleej p6 (26 Sep 2012).jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>934</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="377">Al Khaleej 26/9/2012</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="378">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/Al Khaleej p6 (26 Sep 2012).jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="379"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="380">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/Emarat Alyoum p15 (26 Sep 2012).jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>935</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="381">Emarat Alyoum 26/9/2012</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="382">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/Emarat Alyoum p15 (26 Sep 2012).jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="383"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="384">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/26 Sep 2012/DMCA Taskforce.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>932</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="385">Task Force meeting</b:Title><b:Url z:Ref="369" i:nil="true"/></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="386">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government authority charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has revealed that the Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force met with the representatives from the cruise industry to discuss the priorities for the 2012/13 cruise season. </a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="387">DMCA hosts Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force meeting to discuss priorities for new cruise season   </a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="388"><Comments z:Id="389" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="390" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">EmanCSR</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-12-18T11:03:54</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">280</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="391" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/1 Oct 2012,/DM Creek Team.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="392" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/1 Oct 2012,/DM Creek Team.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="393" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="394" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="395" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dm.supports.dmw.2012.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="396">&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In line with Dubai&amp;rsquo;s vision to be a regional and global trade and economic hub and a preferred host of prestigious international events, Dubai Municipality has announced its full support to the first-ever Dubai Maritime Week 2012 to be held in November. In appreciation of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s long-standing maritime heritage, Dubai Municipality will conduct a full-day presentation on how Dubai Creek has become one of the world&amp;rsquo;s premier heritage landmarks.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eng. Rashad Bukhash, Director of Architectural Heritage Department, Dubai Municipality, said: &amp;ldquo;We appreciate the efforts of Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) to organize this important event. Our support to Dubai Maritime Week 2012 is in line with our goal to stimulate government participation in key industry initiatives, which help validate the UAE&amp;rsquo;s position as a leading destination for high-profile international events. As part of our commitment to maintain and protect historical sites in the emirate in general, and in line with our efforts at the Architectural Heritage Department to enlist Dubai Creek as a World Heritage Site in particular, we are glad to organize a dedicated workshop during Dubai Maritime Week to discuss various aspects about Dubai Creek, in the presence of international experts and professionals from different industries. This move is an opportunity to shed light on this important water passage and its role in boosting trade and economic growth, as well as its contribution towards the general development of the emirate over the past decades.&amp;rdquo; &lt;br /&gt;
Organized in collaboration with several strategic partners from Dubai Government, Dubai Maritime Week 2012 will host a range of maritime industry-related activities and events, including conferences, panel discussions and forums, as well as public-oriented activities to celebrate Dubai's maritime heritage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amer Ali, CEO, Dubai Maritime City Authority, added: &amp;ldquo;The support of Dubai Municipality and many other government entities reflects their commitment to promote the UAE as an international destination and a hub for major international events, thus creating more opportunities for economic growth and investments. Bounded together by our shared objectives, we aim to contribute to the success of Dubai Maritime Week 2012, which has emerged as one of the most important global events being held in Dubai.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inaugural Dubai Maritime Week 2012 is being organized through the close cooperation between DMCA and Seatrade, one of the leading publishing houses and maritime-related event organizers in the world. The event will feature the &amp;lsquo;Seatrade Middle East &amp;amp; Indian Subcontinent Awards&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Seatrade Middle East Maritime Exhibition &amp;amp; Conference&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Seatrade Middle East Money &amp;amp; Ships Conference&amp;rsquo;. Collectively, these events are poised to provide an ideal platform for local and international maritime professionals, experts, suppliers, economists, analysts and industry financiers to discuss the challenges and urgent issues across the maritime industry.&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="397">Dubai Municipality supports Dubai Maritime Week 2012</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="398" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-10-01T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="399" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="400">In line with Dubai’s vision to be a regional and global trade and economic hub and a preferred host of prestigious international events, Dubai Municipality has announced its full support to the first-ever Dubai Maritime Week 2012 to be held in November. In appreciation of Dubai’s long-standing maritime heritage, Dubai Municipality will conduct a full-day presentation on how Dubai Creek has become one of the world’s premier heritage landmarks.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="401">Dubai Municipality supports Dubai Maritime Week 2012</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="402"><Comments z:Id="403" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="404" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">EmanCSR</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-12-18T12:14:59</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">282</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImageFullURL z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="405" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="406" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="407" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dtccm.supports.dmw.2012</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="408">&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubai Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM) has announced its full support to the first-ever Dubai Maritime Week 2012 to be held in November. DTCM will support the marine workshop to be held on the sidelines of the event, which will discuss all maritime related issues and marine tourism affairs in Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the support of DTCM to Dubai Maritime Week 2012, Hamad Bin Mohammed Bin Mejren, Executive Director of Business Tourism, said: &amp;ldquo;Hosting this global event reaffirms Dubai&amp;rsquo;s exalted international status, which has been achieved due to the emirate&amp;rsquo;s visionary leadership and their support for various events taking place here. The continuous efforts of Dubai Maritime City Authority and all the strategic partners of the government bodies in Dubai have also been noteworthy.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We are proud to be part of this global event hosted in Dubai for the first time and to participate in several activities, especially those related to marine tourism, which is playing a crucial role in channeling infrastructure development investments in Dubai,&amp;rdquo; he added.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amer Ali, CEO, Dubai Maritime City Authority, added: &amp;ldquo;The support of Dubai Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing reaffirms their confidence in the potential of this event in stimulating tourism and attracting more investments into this sector, especially marine tourism. The marine workshop to be held on the sidelines of the event will significantly contribute to boosting the quality and efficiency of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s maritime sector and to ensure greater safety for all marine activities in the waters of the emirate.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organized in collaboration with several strategic partners from Dubai Government, Dubai Maritime Week 2012 will host a range of maritime industry-related activities and events, including conferences, panel discussions and forums, as well as public-oriented activities to celebrate Dubai's maritime heritage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inaugural Dubai Maritime Week 2012 is being organized through the close cooperation between DMCA and Seatrade, one of the leading publishing houses and maritime-related event organizers in the world. The event will feature the &amp;lsquo;Seatrade Middle East &amp;amp; Indian Subcontinent Awards&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Seatrade Middle East Maritime Exhibition &amp;amp; Conference&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Seatrade Middle East Money &amp;amp; Ships Conference&amp;rsquo;. &lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="409">Dubai Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing supports Dubai Maritime Week 2012</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="410" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-10-11T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="411" z:Size="0" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="412">Dubai Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM) has announced its full support to the first-ever Dubai Maritime Week 2012 to be held in November. DTCM will support the marine workshop to be held on the sidelines of the event, which will discuss all maritime related issues and marine tourism affairs in Dubai.

</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="413">Dubai Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing supports Dubai Maritime Week 2012</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="414"><Comments z:Id="415" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="416" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">EmanCSR</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-12-18T15:10:13</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">286</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="417" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 Oct 2012,/marina.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="418" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 Oct 2012,/marina.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="419" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="420" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="421" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.marina.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="422">&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government authority charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, recently concluded a public private partnership (PPP)&amp;nbsp; Forum with the senior management of the flagship marinas in Dubai. The PPP Marina Initiative Management is one of several such DMCA-led initiatives underway in the Emirate.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In collaboration with other government stakeholders, DMCA is driving a consensus process to enhance existing marina measures, standardize best management practices and manage critical sustainable aspects of the industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marina Management welcomed the opportunity to discuss their desire for greater local regulation regarding the licensing of personnel operating leisure and pleasure craft; innovative approaches to calls for marine assistance that are non emergency in nature; enhancing existing emergency response plans, procedures and challenges; maritime traffic management; and marina system regulations as they pertain to maritime safety, fire and environmental standards.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMCA agreed to hold quarterly work group meetings with the marinas to ensure that their unique area of operations has a voice in the development of regulations and long term maritime sector strategy as well as reporting on key performance indicators and contributions to the GDP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The agenda was ambitious and the discussions wide ranging, with the flow and depth of information impressive. The initiative has already reaped results with a draft Marina Integrated Waste Management System Regulation being reviewed by the marinas with a comment and implementation deadline set. The Regulation allows for the differences in marina operations, and is written to promote internal and external review and continuous improvement. The regulation outlines the responsibilities of all of the stakeholders including the marina operators in Dubai, the key sections of the waste management plan to be adopted by the marinas, and the responsibilities of boat owners with regard to the environmental-protection policy of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s marinas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally Marina Management now has a single point of contact for reporting navigational hazards, dangerous marine incidents, and potential areas of concern for the marine community in the DMCA&amp;rsquo;s Marine Adviser&amp;rsquo;s Office. The marinas also agreed to explore a mutual aide system whereby each marina would lend assistance to non-members that experience non-life threatening emergencies (run out of gas) in their marinas area of operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amer Ali, CEO of Dubai Maritime City Authority, said: &amp;ldquo;Dubai continues to channel huge investments to develop world-class marinas, unlocking more business and investment opportunities in the emirate&amp;rsquo;s maritime industry while ultimately contributing to the emirate&amp;rsquo;s long-term economic growth strategy. In this regard, marina operators play a very important role in our efforts to expand and strengthen Dubai&amp;rsquo;s maritime sector. The recent meeting with key professionals of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s marine leisure sector is part of our continuing drive to ensure the sustainable growth of the maritime sector and bolster Dubai&amp;rsquo;s reputation as the premier maritime hub in the Middle East.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="423">DMCA’s Public Private Partnership model drives agenda during Marina Senior Management Forum</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="424" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-10-21T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Id="425">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 Oct 2012,/marina.jpg</a:NewsThumbnail><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="426" z:Size="2" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="427"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="428">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 Oct 2012,/marina.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>963</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="429">Marina</b:Title><b:Url z:Ref="425" i:nil="true"/></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="430"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="431">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 Oct 2012,/GulfToday p2 (21 OCt 2012).jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>964</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="432">GulfToday-21/10/2012</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="433">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 Oct 2012,/GulfToday p2 (21 OCt 2012).jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="434">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government authority charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, recently concluded a public private partnership (PPP)  Forum with the senior management of the flagship marinas in Dubai. The PPP Marina Initiative Management is one of several such DMCA-led initiatives underway in the Emirate. </a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="435">DMCA’s Public Private Partnership model drives agenda during Marina Senior Management Forum</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="436"><Comments z:Id="437" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="438" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">EmanCSR</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2012-12-18T15:20:51</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">287</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="439" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/29 Oct 2012/Gulf News (29 Oct 2012).jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="440" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/29 Oct 2012/Gulf News (29 Oct 2012).jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="441" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="442" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="443" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">customs.supports.dmw.2012.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="444">&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In line with Dubai&amp;rsquo;s vision to be a regional and global trade and economic hub and a preferred host of prestigious international events, Dubai Customs has announced its full support to the first-ever Dubai Maritime Week 2012 to be held in November.&lt;br /&gt;
In appreciation of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s long-standing maritime heritage, Dubai Customs will participate in the Dubai Maritime Week 2012 through a special event that will be announced soon. &lt;br /&gt;
Commenting on Dubai Customs&amp;rsquo; support to the Dubai Maritime Week 2012, Yusuf Al Sahlawi, Senior Executive Director, Corporate Affairs, Dubai Customs, said: &amp;ldquo;We appreciate the efforts of Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) to organize this unique event. Our support to Dubai Maritime Week 2012 is in line with our goal to stimulate government participation in key industry initiatives, which help reaffirm the UAE&amp;rsquo;s position as a leading destination for high-profile international events.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Dubai Customs and its employees are proud of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s maritime sector and its long history, and we are glad to take part in Dubai Maritime Week 2012. Our involvement in this event provides us an opportunity to shed light on Dubai Customs&amp;rsquo; contributions towards the success of the emirate&amp;rsquo;s maritime sector which has boosted trade and economic activity, and also contributed towards the overall development of Dubai over the past decades,&amp;rdquo; he added.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;
Organized in collaboration with several strategic partners from Dubai Government, Dubai Maritime Week 2012 will host a range of maritime industry-related activities and events, including conferences, panel discussions and forums, as well as public-oriented activities to celebrate Dubai's maritime heritage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Amer Ali, CEO, Dubai Maritime City Authority, added: &amp;ldquo;The support of Dubai Customs and many other government entities reflects their commitment to promote the UAE as an international destination and a premier hub for major international events, thus creating more opportunities for economic growth and investments. Unified by our shared objectives, we aim to contribute to the success of Dubai Maritime Week 2012, which has emerged as one of the most important global events being held in Dubai.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inaugural Dubai Maritime Week 2012 is being organized through close cooperation between DMCA and Seatrade, one of the leading publishing houses and maritime-related event organizers in the world. The event will feature the &amp;lsquo;Seatrade Middle East &amp;amp; Indian Subcontinent Awards&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Seatrade Middle East Maritime Exhibition &amp;amp; Conference&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Seatrade Middle East Money &amp;amp; Ships Conference&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collectively, these events are poised to provide an ideal platform for local and international maritime professionals, experts, suppliers, economists, analysts and industry financiers to discuss the challenges and urgent issues across the maritime industry.&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="445">Dubai Customs supports Dubai Maritime Week 2012</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="446" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2012-10-29T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="447" z:Size="2" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="448"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="449">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/29 Oct 2012/Gulf News (29 Oct 2012).jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>965</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="450">GulfNews-29/10/2012</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="451">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/29 Oct 2012/Gulf News (29 Oct 2012).jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="452"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="453">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/29 Oct 2012/Khaleej Times (29 Oct 2012).jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>966</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="454">KhaleejTimes-29/10/2012</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="455">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/29 Oct 2012/Khaleej Times (29 Oct 2012).jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="456">In line with Dubai’s vision to be a regional and global trade and economic hub and a preferred host of prestigious international events, Dubai Customs has announced its full support to the first-ever Dubai Maritime Week 2012 to be held in November.</a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="457">Dubai Customs supports Dubai Maritime Week 2012</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="458"><Comments z:Id="459" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="460" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">EmanCSR</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2013-04-10T11:25:02</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">302</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="461" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/25 March 2013/Cruise Drill.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="462" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/25 March 2013/Cruise Drill.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="463" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="464" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="465" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.ship.fire.drill.2013.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="466">&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government authority charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced that the Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force has recently concluded a Ship Board Fire Exercise with Serenade of the Seas.&amp;nbsp; THE SERENADE, a MODERN RCCL cruise ship IS HOME PORTED in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Mina Rashid Cruise Terminal DURING THE TRADITIONAL CRUISE SEASON.&amp;nbsp; The Serenade CARRIES 3,000 guests and 1,000 crew aboard TOWERS 13 FLOORS ABOVE THE SEA AND IS LONGER THAN TWO FOOTBALL FIELDS. The drill was part of DMCA&amp;rsquo;s continuing efforts to improve emergency procedures and collaboration between public and private sector entities in promoting maritime safety and security. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMCA has been organizing similar exercises to test command and control communications protocols of cruise ships and to identify areas for enhancing shore side and ship board preparation and engagement. The drill involved a SIMULATED fire in one of the ship&amp;rsquo;s large tender boats, which are used to ferry guests between the ship and port and are also designated as life boats. THE BOATS MAY CARRY AS MANY AS 200 people. Other agencies that RESPONDED were the CIVIL DEFENSE; IMMIGRATION; Dubai Police, DUBAI RESCUE POLICE;&amp;nbsp; Dubai Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM), Dubai Ports Authority (DPA); Ports, Customs and Free Zone Corporation; Dubai Ports World, AND THE PRIVATE SECTOR INCLUDING THE SHIP&amp;rsquo;S agents. CIVIL DEFENSE RESPONDED WITH THREE TRUCKS INCLUDING AN AERIAL UNIT IN ORDER TO REACH THE AREA INVOLVED IN THE SIMULATION. THE CIVIL DFENSE TEAM WORKED SEAMLESSLY WITH THE SHIP&amp;rsquo;S CREW SETTING UP A UNIFIED COMMAND ON THE SHIP&amp;rsquo;S BRIDGE TO COORDIANTE AND DIRECT THE RESPONSE EFFORTS. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Captain Anders, the Serenade&amp;rsquo;s Master, thanked the Task Force members and stated, this was a good exercise for all of us and it should be repeated at least once a year . &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Amer Ali, Executive Director, Dubai Maritime City Authority, said: &amp;ldquo;The safety and security of guests and crew of ships berthed in Dubai are of utmost priority for us. DMCA is therefore constantly working with THE INDUSTRY ON various initiatives such as fire drills and other exercises to further enhance emergency procedures, collaboration AND COORDINATION with&amp;nbsp; Dubai&amp;rsquo;S Civil Defense team AND THE OTHER EMERGENCY RESPONSDERS. The drill we conducted with the cruise ship &amp;lsquo;Serenade of the Seas&amp;rsquo; highlighted the cohesiveness of the Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force and the high level of preparedness of THE SHIP&amp;rsquo;S STAFF AND THE SHORESIDE SUPPORT STAKEHOLDERS. DMCA will continue to proactively introduce initiatives that will further broaden our understanding and expertise in dealing with various emergency situations, while helping reaffirm the status of Dubai as a genuinely safe and secure cruise ship destination.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMCA has recently introduced several initiatives that have added new layers of safety and protection for the maritime sector, including new regulations for the deployment of navigation aids (navaids) by Dubai-based maritime agencies. The Authority also organized major networking and industry events recently, including Dubai Maritime Week 2012, the first-ever maritime industry workshop in Dubai, and the Public Private Partnership (PPP) Forum with senior management of marinas in Dubai. During these events, DMCA discussed important maritime topics, including existing emergency response plans; maritime traffic management; PLACES OF REFUGE; MARITIME ARBITRATION; MARINE ACCIDENT INVESTIGATIONS; VESSEL GENERAL PERMITS; marina system regulations; and maritime safety, fire and environmental standards.&lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="467">DMCA conduct’s Ship Board Fire Exercise on ‘Serenade of the Seas’a</a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="468" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2013-03-25T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Id="469">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/25 March 2013/Cruise Drill.jpg</a:NewsThumbnail><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="470" z:Size="3" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="471"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="472">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/25 March 2013/Cruise Drill.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>981</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="473">Cruise Drill</b:Title><b:Url z:Ref="469" i:nil="true"/></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="474"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="475">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/25 March 2013/Al Bayan p4 (25 March 2013).jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>982</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="476">Al Bayan</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="477">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/25 March 2013/Al Bayan p4 (25 March 2013).jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="478"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="479">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/25 March 2013/Al Khaleej p7 (25 March 2013).jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>983</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="480">Al Khaleej</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="481">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/25 March 2013/Al Khaleej p7 (25 March 2013).jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="482">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA), the government authority charged with regulating, coordinating and supervising all aspects of the maritime sector in Dubai, has announced that the Cruise Ship Emergency Response Task Force has recently concluded a Ship Board Fire Exercise with Serenade of the Seas.  THE SERENADE, a MODERN RCCL cruise ship IS HOME PORTED in Dubai’s Mina Rashid Cruise Terminal DURING THE TRADITIONAL CRUISE SEASON.  The Serenade CARRIES 3,000 guests and 1,000 crew aboard TOWERS 13 FLOORS ABOVE THE SEA AND IS LONGER THAN TWO FOOTBALL FIELDS. The drill was part of DMCA’s continuing efforts to improve emergency procedures and collaboration between public and private sector entities in promoting maritime safety and security. </a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="483">DMCA conduct’s Ship Board Fire Exercise on ‘Serenade of the Seas’</a:Title></a:NewsView><a:NewsView z:Id="484"><Comments z:Id="485" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><CreatedBy z:Id="486" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">EmanCSR</CreatedBy><CreatedDate xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">2013-04-22T10:38:07</CreatedDate><EndDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><GeoCoordinateX xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateX><GeoCoordinateY xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">0</GeoCoordinateY><ID xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">308</ID><Keywords z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MainImage z:Id="487" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 April 2013/Jet Skis Usages Map-english.jpg</MainImage><MainImageFullURL z:Id="488" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 April 2013/Jet Skis Usages Map-english.jpg</MainImageFullURL><MetaPageDescription z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><MetaPageTitle z:Ref="5" i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ModuleType z:Id="489" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">NewsDAL.Model.News</ModuleType><Published xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">true</Published><Ratings z:Id="490" z:Size="0" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><ShowInHomePage xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">false</ShowInHomePage><StartDate i:nil="true" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"/><UniqueName z:Id="491" xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model">dmca.jetski.locations.2013.e</UniqueName><a:AuthorComments z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:AuthorName z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Content z:Id="492">&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) has cleared the use of jet skis across Dubai&amp;rsquo;s coastline, with the introduction of new rules that cover allocation of resting areas for jet skis, following the approval from Dubai Executive Council&amp;rsquo;s Health and Safety Committee. This move is based on a comprehensive study that assessed maritime traffic movement on Dubai&amp;rsquo;s inshore waters and beaches. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to this, 300-metre buffer zones have been imposed around three Dubai beaches at Dubai Marina, Umm Suqeim 1 and 2 and Jumeirah 2 and 3 to keep jet skis out of swimming areas. This is the result of DMCA&amp;rsquo;s mutual cooperation and ongoing collaboration with Dubai Municipality, Dubai Police and other relevant parties. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Safety Measures &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DMCA has further introduced a range of safety measures that need to be taken while using a jet ski, including but not limited to: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Water sports activities can only be undertaken between sunrise and sunset &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Life jacket must be worn at all times when in waters &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Do not exceed the limit for number of passengers allowed onboard &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Be aware of the traffic, take caution, respect speed limits and leave a safe distance from other watercrafts and floating objects &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Do not attempt any activities in waterways or entrances and exits of marinas, ports and resting areas &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Do not attempt any activities near restricted areas &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Children below 16 years must be accompanied by a guardian &lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Do not attempt any activities near the shores marked by yellow buoys&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Jet skis are allowed to stay at the resting areas for rest only, and must abide by the speed limits when entering and existing these areas &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amer Ali, Executive Director, Dubai Maritime City Authority, said: &amp;ldquo;Maritime safety is vital to reinforce confidence in the local maritime industry and further improve its competitiveness and promote Dubai as one of the leading international maritime destinations. The safety-oriented initiatives are set to pave the way for a safe, vibrant maritime sector and therefore support the economic growth in Dubai, in accordance with the highest standards of excellence.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Allocating certain areas for the use of jet skis is a strategic step forward in building on our efforts to regulate the sector and maintain the highest standards of maritime safety and best international practices. We look forward to continuing on our path of success in cooperation with our strategic partners from various government authorities and industry-related entities in Dubai, while also maintaining the hard work to set maritime regulations in line with the rapidly evolving developments, in order to consolidate Dubai&amp;rsquo;s leading position as a first-class international maritime hub,&amp;rdquo; Ali concluded.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;</a:Content><a:Headline z:Id="493">Dubai Maritime City Authority open jet ski usage in Dubai, announces resting areas </a:Headline><a:Language z:Id="494" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:Active>true</b:Active><b:ID>1</b:ID><b:LangCode z:Ref="14" i:nil="true"/><b:LanguageCulture z:Ref="15" i:nil="true"/><b:Name z:Ref="16" i:nil="true"/></a:Language><a:NewsDate>2013-04-21T00:00:00</a:NewsDate><a:NewsThumbnail z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:RelatedEntities z:Id="495" z:Size="2" xmlns:b="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/ProdigyDAL.Model"><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="496"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="497">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 April 2013/Jet Skis Usages Map-english.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>1096</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="498">Jet Skis Usages Map</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="499">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 April 2013/Jet Skis Usages Map-english.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView><b:RelatedEntitiesView z:Id="500"><b:Description z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><b:FullUrl z:Id="501">http://demoserver.tacme.net:3030/DMCAWebsiteV2/Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 April 2013/Gulf news.jpg</b:FullUrl><b:ID>1097</b:ID><b:OrderNumber>0</b:OrderNumber><b:RelatedType>Image</b:RelatedType><b:Title z:Id="502">Gulf news</b:Title><b:Url z:Id="503">Data/Images/NewsImageEn/21 April 2013/Gulf news.jpg</b:Url></b:RelatedEntitiesView></a:RelatedEntities><a:Source z:Ref="5" i:nil="true"/><a:Summary z:Id="504">Dubai Maritime City Authority (DMCA) has cleared the use of jet skis across Dubai’s coastline, with the introduction of new rules that cover allocation of resting areas for jet skis, following the approval from Dubai Executive Council’s Health and Safety Committee. This move is based on a comprehensive study that assessed maritime traffic movement on Dubai’s inshore waters and beaches. </a:Summary><a:Title z:Id="505">Dubai Maritime City Authority open jet ski usage in Dubai, announces resting areas </a:Title></a:NewsView></SearchNewsResult></SearchNewsResponse></s:Body></s:Envelope>